

Monika Krikščiūnienė

User's info

Date of birth: 1990.07.27 (26 y)

City: Vilnius

Phone: +37061339947

E-mail: rudytemonik@gmail.com

After finishing web development studies I've started my career as a Junior Developer - gained experience in building projects using React, ASAP.NET. Later I tooked the chalange and joined NFQ Technologies Academy where I'm improving my skills in OOP, PHP, Git, Symfony, Doctrine, Bootstrap, etc.

Also I'm mentee at "WomenGoTech" mentorship programm.

Work experience

2017.03 - Present

Company: NFQ Academy

Position: Intern

Description: NFQ Academy is the leading series of free lectures and workshops in Lithuania for students interested in software development. During Academy I'm improving my skills in OOP, PHP, Git, Symfony, Doctrine, Bootstrap, etc.

2017.01 - Present

Company: WomenGoTech mentorship program

Position: Mentee

Description: "Women Go Tech" is a mentorship program, organized by leading Lithuanian organizations INFOBALT, "Telia Lietuva" and Global Shapers Vilnius Hub.

2017.02 - 2017.04

Company: SolutionLab Production Position: Junior Developer

Description: Software development using React, ASP.NET, etc.

2014.06 - 2016.06

Company: vipcommunications

Company site: www.vipcommunications.lt/lt/titulinis.html

Position: Junior account manager

Description: Preparation and implementation of public relation projects. Collaboration with the media. Communication with clients and third parties. Creative writing.

Education

2016 - 2017

Educational institution: 3W Academy Lithuania

Specialty: Web developer Degree: Professional

2011 - 2015

Educational institution: VGTU

Specialty: Bachelor of Communications and Information

Degree: Higher/Bachelor

Languages

Language	Speaking	Understanding	Writing
English	Good	Good	Good
German	Average	Average	Average
Lithuanian	Perfect	Perfect	Perfect

Computer knowledge

Software

AutoCAD: 1-2 years Coreldraw: up to 1 year Excel: 3-4 years

Photoshop: 4 and more years PowerPoint: 4 and more years Word: 4 and more years

Additional information

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

PHP, Symfony, Laravel, JavaScript, React, jQuery, SQL, HTML, CSS, LESS,

Bootstrap, Git, Ajax, Wordpress.

Other info

Driver licence: B Experience: 6 y

Hobbies: I always enjoy to try something new in my free time: visit and explore some new places, taste different food, etc. Probably you could be interested to talk about movies or music with me. Also, I'm a passionate cook – I really like to try new recipes

or bake something my own.